question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
